http://www.klsecurity.com/terms-conditions#keeping

Privacy & Security
KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc., Inc. Privacy Statement
KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc., Inc. ("KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc.", "we", "us", "our") appreciates the value of information and respects your right to privacy. We also understand the inherent privacy risks involved in using the Internet. We feel strongly about our own privacy when we visit web sites, subscribe to services, or download software. We want to provide the same privacy for you here that we want for ourselves when we visit other sites.
We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information we may collect through this web site ("Site") and how such information may be used and/or shared with others. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, because by using this Site you are acknowledging that you understand and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may from time to time modify this Privacy Policy, and the modified Privacy Policy will be effective upon posting. Please return to this page and check the "Last updated" date to make sure you understand and agree to the latest Privacy Policy. Your use of this Site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy.
Note that this Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected through this Site and not through any other sources. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms of Use posted on this Site.
Your California Privacy Rights
The following only applies to California residents.
We do not share your personally identifiable information with our affiliates, sponsors, partners, advertisers or other third parties for their direct marketing purposes.
For more information on how your personally identifiable information is collected and used, please read the remainder of our Privacy Policy.
Children Under 13
This Site is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age, except for the limited circumstances described below. In the event a child under the age of 13 submits a question to us on this Site and identifies his or her age, we may use the child's e-mail address for the sole purpose of responding to the child's question on a one-time-only basis. However, we will not use the child's e-mail address to re-contact the child and we will delete it from our records once we have responded. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, we will make reasonable efforts to delete such information from our records.
Your Information and How We Use It
This Site collects two types of information: (1) information that personally identifies you that you provide directly when you use various KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc., Inc. services or participate in various KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc., Inc. programs (such as your name and e-mail address); and (2) information that does not personally identify you that may be gathered by means such as analyzing page views and user navigation patterns (such as the number of users who log onto this Site on a daily basis).
Personally Identifiable Information
As a general policy, no personally identifiable information is automatically collected from your visit to this Site. However, in certain circumstances, you may be asked to provide us with some specific information about yourself in order to use certain features on this Site or to take advantage of certain opportunities that we may offer through this Site. For example:
We may need to share your personal information with certain third parties such as our agents, service providers and other representatives acting on our behalf for limited purposes. For example, we may share personal information to third parties to perform services on our behalf such as:
Fulfilling our customers' orders
Sending KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. marketing communications
Delivering packages
Scheduling and performing installations
Servicing products
Fulfilling subscription services
Conducting research, analysis or administering surveys
Sending regular mail and e-mail on behalf of KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc.
Processing credit card payments
The third parties we conduct business with are only authorized to use your information to perform the service for which they were hired.
Registration: You do not need to register in order to access this Site. However, if you wish to use certain features of this Site or participate in certain programs offered through this Site, you may need to register. In order to register, you will be asked to create a user name and password, as well as provide certain personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. In addition, there may be additional registration requirements in connection with a particular feature or program. We will use your e-mail address to provide you with the products and services that are offered in connection with the applicable features and/or programs for which you have registered, and, if requested, to provide customer service and technical support. We may also send you e-mails relating to technical issues in order to resolve a prior issue or to proactively notify you of technical or other issues that may affect you and/or your use of this Site. If you wish to update your account information, log into your account. If you forget your password, you can reset it via the registered user sign-in page. If you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know by e-mail at contact@klsecurity.com
Purchase and Return: If you purchase and/or return any products through this Site, you will be asked to provide your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit/debit card information and billing information, as applicable. This information will be used to process your purchase order or return. We will also use your e-mail address to provide you with information and notices regarding your purchase or return.
Warranty and Product Registration: If you purchase any products through this Site or through other means, you will have the option to register your product and/or product warranty through this Site by completing and submitting an online registration form. In order to complete the form and register your product or warranty, you will be asked to create a user name and password, as well as provide certain personally identifiable information, such as your name, e-mail address and telephone number. We will use your e-mail address to send you information about product updates and additional compatible products or services that are offered, and, if requested, to provide customer service. In addition, we may use your personally identifiable information to provide you with information about your purchasing history.
Newsletters and Information about Products, Services, Programs and Promotions: If you wish to receive our online newsletter and/or information about our products, services, programs and promotions, you will be asked to provide your e-mail address.
Please note that any information you submit on this Site will be used (i) to authenticate your identity for access to our services and accessing shared files (if applicable), (ii) to carry out your requests and respond to your inquiries, (iii) in accordance with the terms set forth herein, and (iv) as otherwise disclosed at the point where such information is collected or in any additional terms and conditions applicable to the particular feature of this Site. Please also note that in order to carry out your requests, to make various features, services and materials available to you through this Site, and to respond to your inquiries, we may share your personally identifiable information with third parties that perform functions on our behalf (or on behalf of our partners), such as companies or individuals that analyze data, provide customer service, participate in or administer our promotions or provide marketing or promotional assistance (but such information will be shared only to the extent they need such information to perform their functions). Your personally identifiable information may also be used by us or shared with our subsidiaries, affiliates, sponsors, partners, advertisers or other third parties to provide you with product information and promotional and other offers. You may always direct us not to share your personally identifiable information with third parties, not to use your personally identifiable information to provide you with any such information or offers, or not to send you newsletters by sending us an e-mail at contact@klsecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. Except as provided herein, your personally identifiable information will not be provided to any third parties without prior approval from you.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
From time to time we may collect general, non-personally identifiable, statistical information about the use of this Site, such as how many visitors visit a specific page on this Site, how long they stay on that page, and which hyperlinks, if any, they "click" on. We collect this information through the use of technologies such as "cookies" and "IP addresses", which are discussed in greater detail below. We collect this information in order to determine which areas of this Site are most popular and to enhance this Site for visitors. From time to time we may also collect general, non-personally identifiable, statistical information about information and data stored and shared through the personal servers and the services we provide to support personal servers ("Web Service"). We may also group this information into aggregate data in order to describe the use of this Site to our existing or potential business partners, sponsors, advertisers or other third parties, or in response to a government request. However, please be assured that this aggregate data will in no way personally identify you or any other visitors to this Site.
IP Addresses
An IP address is a unique number assigned to your computer when it accesses the Internet or another computer network. Web servers and network devices automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We collect IP addresses for purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to track the use of this Site. When visitors request pages from this Site, our servers log the visitors' IP addresses. It is not our practice to link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a visitor's session will be logged, but the visitor remains anonymous to us. However, we reserve the right to use IP addresses to identify a visitor only when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with this Site's policies or to protect our services, members, this Site, or others.
Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to a device accessing the Internet. Cookies make web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at this Site. Most web sites use cookies. By showing how and when visitors use this Site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Information such as the total number of visitors and pages viewed is most easily tracked with cookies. We may use the information from cookies to make improvements and updates to this Site and to tailor our services to our visitors' needs.
You always have the option of disabling cookies using your browser preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your browser. However, please be aware that some features of this Site may not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers or other third parties with links on this Site. We do not control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry.
We reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable or non-personally identifiable information if we are required to do so by law or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary in order to: (a) fulfill a government request; (b) conform with the requirements of the law or to comply with legal process served on us; (c) to protect or defend our legal rights or property, this Site, or its users; or (d) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of this Site's users or the general public.
Surveys
From time to time, we may conduct surveys on this Site. If you decide to participate, you may be asked to provide certain demographic information (such as your gender, date of birth and zip code). We may use the information that you submit, including your responses to the survey questionnaires, for the purpose(s) identified to you prior to your participation in the survey. In some cases, we may publish the results of the survey, but only as aggregate information. As we may be conducting certain surveys with our advertisers, sponsors or other third parties, we may also share the results of such surveys with such third parties, but in no event will the results personally identify you.
Choice
You can choose not to receive any newsletter, e-mail or other communication from us by (i) following the removal instructions in the communication that you receive, or (ii) e-mailing us at: contact@klsecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. If you choose to e-mail us, please be sure to attach a copy of the unwanted communication.
Keeping Your Information Secure
Secure Credit Card Transactions
When you provide us with any personal information, such as your credit card number when making a purchase, we use SSL data encryption to ensure that no one can read as it is transmitted over the Internet. We use Cookies (small encrypted data files containing references to user ID information that are stored on our secure server and may write to your hard drive) to keep track of your shopping cart. Your information is safely stored behind a firewall that protects it from users from other networks.
Disclaimer: KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. is dedicated to continually improving its websites by adding new functionality, products, services and programs. Because of those improvements, along with the changes in the law, technology, and KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc.'s business, KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. The latest version of our privacy policy will be available on our web site and will indicate the date that it went into effect. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you use this website to make sure you always understand how your information will be used.
At KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. we protect your credit card information and privacy by using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology (the industry standard security protocol), hosting our site on secure servers, and maintaining Secure Site status from GeoTrust, the security industry leader.
Removal From KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc..Com Lists
You may receive periodic emails or postal mailings from us with information on new products and services, or upcoming events. If you do not want to receive e-mail and/ or postal mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an email at contact@klsecurity.com
Links To Other Sites
KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.
We have reasonable and appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information.
Transfer of Assets
As we continue to develop our business, we may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or all or substantially all of our assets, or assets related to this Site, personally identifiable information, non-personally identifiable information, and any other information that we have collected about the users of this Site will be transferred to such entity as one of the transferred assets. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, all such information may be considered an asset of ours and as such may be sold or transferred to third parties.
Other Sites
This Site may contain links to other web sites that we do not control or maintain. We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by these other web sites. We encourage you to note when you leave this Site and to read the privacy statements of such other web sites before submitting any personally identifiable information.
Processing of Data Outside the EU
Given that we are an international business, our use of your information necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis (including the United States and countries outside the European Union).
Your Right to See Your Information
The following only applies to EU residents.
In addition to your normal access to your Web Account information, you have a right to see the personal information held about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information we hold about you, please send an e-mail to contact@klsecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc.
Returns & Replacements
RETURN POLICY.
All returns must comply with the return procedure set forth below, and all returned items must be in new condition, including the original box, packaging, manuals and accessories. No refunds or exchanges are allowed after 30 days from the date of receipt, or if the UPC code has been removed from the packaging. A restocking fee may be applied equal to 25% of the purchase price will be charged on any opened item, unless the item is defective; or exchanged for the same or a similar item. The 25% restocking fee will be assessed at the time of refund or exchange. Original shipping charges are not refundable.
FREIGHT DAMAGE AND DISCREPANCY
Merchandise should be fully inspected upon receipt for evidence of damage or shortage before signing the delivery receipt. If damage or shortage is evident, it must be noted on the delivery receipt and K.L. Security Enterprises, inc. notified in writing within 3 business days.
If external appearance does not indicate damage, but damage is discovered upon unpacking:
1) Save all packing materials.
2) Report concealed damage within 7 days of delivery.
a) For prepaid shipments, contact our Customer Service Department immediately. If product has been moved from point of delivery K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. will not be responsible for any damage.
b) For collect shipments, contact your carrier immediately to request inspection and reimbursement of product cost.
K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. is not responsible for reimbursement when delivery receipts are signed clear of damage/discrepancy, or when concealed damage is reported after 7 days.
REQUEST FOR RETURN MERCHANDISE
K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. assumes no obligation to accept the return or provide credit for any unit damaged during installation unless installers are agents of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc.
K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. assumes no obligation to accept the return or provide credit for merchandise which conforms to product specification within the warranty period.  In the event that the merchandise does not conform, is defective, or if there are special circumstances which would reasonably require the return of merchandise, the dealer who ordered the merchandise must obtain return authorization by calling Order Entry for return authorization.
Return shipments will not be accepted or credited without a return authorization number. Returns will be subject to charges which may include the following:
1) Transportation Costs
2) Handling Charges
3) Refurbishing Costs
4) Restocking Fees
Return shipments must be properly packaged to prevent shipping damage. Any items returned with freight damage due to improper packaging will not be allowed for credit. Shipping costs for non-defective returns are the returnee’s responsibility. K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. will not accept return of special order, factory-modified or discontinued products unless found to be defective and so reported within 30 days after receipt of merchandise.  K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. will not accept return of non-warranty product.
REPAIRS AND ADJUSTMENTS
Invoice deductions for repairs or adjustments cannot be honored unless authorized in advance by Technical Support. For authorization and assistance, please call (866) 867-0306
CHANGES
K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. reserves the right to make changes at any time in regard to price, product specification, stocking location and design without notice.
RETURNS PROCEDURE. To return an item, contact Customer Support at contact@klsecurity.com or (765) 463-7972 to obtain a Return Authorization (RMA) number. RMA numbers are valid for 30 days from the date of issuance. We are unable to accept returns without an RMA number. All returns must be shipped prepaid.
Payment, Pricing & Promotions
PRICING, SPECIFICATIONS AND AVAILABILITY
Prices, specifications and availability of products are subject to change without notice. Due to the changing nature of the internet market, and because of the technical differences in the equipment of our customers, product descriptions may not reflect current technical information, and KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. cannot be responsible for photographic differences in product size, shape and color.
KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. orders generate an automatic confirmation e-mail, but the receipt of a confirmation only means that we have received your order, and does not constitute an offer to sell. We may change our pricing, product description or specifications after any confirmation e-mail, but prior to shipment, due to errors, changing market conditions, product discontinuation or unavailability, typographical errors, or any other reason. We reserve the right to limit the quantity of any item sold, or prohibit a sale altogether.
KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. will notify you of any corrections or changes to your order, and will not complete it until we have your approval. Published prices do not include shipping, sales tax and insurance. We are required by law to collect sales tax on all shipments to Indiana.
Terms of Use
KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC.,
TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC. SITE USE
Entering this site constitutes your acceptance of these Terms and Conditions.
PLEASE READ CAREFULLY. THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS ("TERMS") GOVERN YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF THIS KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC. WEBSITE ("SITE"). SOME CONTENT ACCESSIBLE THROUGH THIS SITE IS SUBJECT TO ADDITIONAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS. TO THE EXTENT THAT ANY PROVISION OF THOSE ADDITIONAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS CONFLICTS WITH THESE TERMS, THOSE ADDITIONAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS WILL PREVAIL. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE TERMS, DO NOT USE THIS SITE. YOUR USE OF THIS SITE INDICATES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS.
GENERAL. KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC. DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE CONTENTS OF THIS SITE ARE ERROR-FREE. INFORMATION ON THIS SITE MAY CONTAIN TECHNICAL INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL OR OTHER TYPES OF ERRORS AND MAY BE CHANGED OR UPDATED AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE. KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC. MAY ALSO MAKE IMPROVEMENTS OR CHANGES IN THE PRODUCTS OR PROGRAMS DESCRIBED ON THIS SITE AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE. KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC. WILL USE REASONABLE EFFORTS TO PLACE ACCURATE AND UP-TO-DATE INFORMATION ON THIS SITE BUT MAKES NO WARRANTY OF ITS ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS OR TIMELINESS. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOUR USE OF ANY INFORMATION AVAILABLE THROUGH THIS SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK.
WARRANTY DISCLAIMER. THE MATERIALS ON THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT POSSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC. DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT OR OTHER VIOLATION OF RIGHTS. KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC. DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE, VALIDITY, ACCURACY, OR RELIABILITY OF, OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF, OR OTHERWISE RESPECTING, THE MATERIALS ON THIS SITE OR ANY SITES LINKED TO THIS SITE.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. IN NO EVENT SHALL KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC., ITS SUBSIDIARIES OR AFFILIATES, OR THEIR RESPECTIVE PARTNERS, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, SHAREHOLDERS, REPRESENTATIVES OR AGENTS (COLLECTIVELY, "KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC.") BE LIABLE FOR DIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE, OR INDIRECT DAMAGES (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, LOSS OF DATA, USE OR PROFITS), HOWEVER CAUSED, WHETHER FOR BREACH OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, OR OTHERWISE, AND WHETHER OR NOT KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC. HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF ANY SUCH DAMAGES. YOU AGREE THAT KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC.'S MAXIMUM LIABILITY ARISING FROM ANY PRODUCT SOLD BY KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC. SHALL NOT EXCEED THE PRICE OF SUCH PRODUCT NOTWITHSTANDING THE KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC. PROTECTION PLAN. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OF EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR CERTAIN DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU TO THE EXTENT SUCH JURISDICTION'S LAW IS APPLICABLE TO THIS AGREEMENT.
PRICING, SPECIFICATIONS AND AVAILABILITY
Prices, specifications and availability of products are subject to change without notice. Due to the changing nature of the internet, and because of the technical differences in the equipment of our customers, product descriptions may not reflect current technical information, and KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. cannot be responsible for photographic differences in product size, shape and color.
KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. orders generate an automatic confirmation e-mail, but the receipt of a confirmation only means that we have received your order, and does not constitute an offer to sell. We may change our pricing, product description or specifications after any confirmation e-mail, but prior to shipment, due to errors, changing market conditions, product discontinuation or unavailability, typographical errors, or any other reason. We reserve the right to limit the quantity of any item sold, or prohibit a sale altogether.
KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. will notify you of any corrections or changes to your order, and will not complete it until we have your approval. Published prices do not include shipping, sales tax and insurance. We are required by law to collect sales tax on all shipments to California.
CUSTOMER INFORMATION
KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. does not currently rent, sell or otherwise forward your name to other companies. To learn more about how KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. protects customer information, please see our Privacy and Security Policy.
PAYMENT AND SHIPPING INFORMATION
PAYING BY CREDIT CARD. You may pay by Visa, MasterCard and American Express. We do not add any credit card surcharges. Please see our Security and Privacy Statement for more information about your credit card safety.
SHIPPING. We ship only to locations within the United States by United Parcel Service ("UPS"), Federal Express (FedEx) or United States Postal Service. KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. cannot be responsible for lost or damaged packages. UPS and FedEx charges include prepaid insurance up to the limits specified by UPS and FedEx. If your package is sent by UPS or FedEx and is lost or damaged, you may contact UPS or FedEx. For your protection, all shipments require a signature at the delivery point. KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to cancel any orders submitted for shipment to a freight forwarder or similar entity.
RETURNS
RETURN POLICY. KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. products are sold through many distributors and resellers throughout the world. All KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. products that were not purchased directly through www.KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. must be returned through the seller you purchased the KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. product from. If you purchased your KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. product directly from www.KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc..com, please follow the instructions below.
All returns must comply with the return procedure set forth below, and all returned items must be in new condition, including the original box, packaging, manuals and accessories. No refunds or exchanges are allowed after 30 days from the date of receipt, or if the UPC code has been removed from the packaging. A restocking fee may be applied equal to 25% of the purchase price will be charged on any opened item, unless the item is defective; or exchanged for the same or a similar item. The 15% restocking fee will be assessed at the time of refund or exchange. Original shipping charges are not refundable.
RETURNS PROCEDURE. To return an item, contact Customer Support at contact@klsecurity.com or (765) 463-7972 to obtain a Return Authorization (RMA) number. RMA numbers are valid for 30 days from the date of issuance. We are unable to accept returns without an RMA number. All returns must be shipped prepaid.
COPYRIGHT AND TRADEMARK. The copyright in all material provided on this Site is held by KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. or by the original creator of the material. Except as stated in this paragraph, none of the material may be copied, reproduced, distributed, republished, downloaded, displayed, posted, framed or transmitted in any form or by any means, including, but not limited to, electronic, mechanical, photocopying, recording, or otherwise, without the prior written permission of KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. or the copyright owner. Permission is granted to display, copy, distribute and download the materials on this Site for personal, non-commercial use only, provided that you do not modify the materials and that you retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the materials. You also may not, without KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc.'s permission, "mirror" any material contained on this Site on any other server. This permission terminates automatically if you breach any of these terms or conditions. Upon termination, you must immediately destroy any downloaded or printed materials. Any unauthorized use of any material contained on this Site may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, and communications regulations and statutes.
MISCELLANEOUS
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES. We provide links to third party sites for your convenience. The inclusion of any link does not imply our endorsement of the site. When you link to a third party site, you leave the KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc.com site. The linked sites are not under our control and we are not responsible for the content of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY FOR USE OF THE KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC. SITE. KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. provides this site and its contents on an "AS IS" basis. We makes no warranty or representation as to this site, either express or implied, including the warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, and non-infringement.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR USE OF THE KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC.SITE. KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC. IS NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE OR OTHER INDIRECT DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM THE USE OF, OR THE INABILITY TO USE, THIS SITE OR ITS CONTENT, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IN NO EVENT SHALL KLSECURITY.COM, A DIVISION OF K.L. SECURITY ENTERPRISES, INC.'S TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES, AND CAUSES OF ACTION RESULTING FROM YOUR USE OF THIS SITE, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NEGLIGENCE) OR OTHERWISE, EXCEED US $1.00.
JURISDICTION AND GOVERNING LAW. This Site is maintained, controlled, operated and administered by KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. from within the United States of America (U.S.). KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. makes no representation that materials at this site are appropriate for use at locations outside of the U.S. and access to this Site from countries where its content or operation is illegal is prohibited. You may not use this Site or export information or products available on this site in violation of U.S. export laws and regulations. All KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. products are controlled for export and end-use by the U.S. government. KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. products may not be exported to Cuba, Iran, Libya, North Korea, Sudan, Syria, or any other country hereafter restricted by the U.S. Government, and they may not be used in the production or distribution of chemical, biological, or nuclear weapons of mass destruction. If you access this Site from a location outside of the U.S., you are responsible for compliance with all local laws. The use of this site, its content and these Terms is governed by the laws of the State of California, without regard to its conflict of laws provisions. Any legal proceeding arising out of the use of this Site, its content or these Terms must be brought in the closest court of competent jurisdiction in or near Auburn, California and must be brought within one year after the claim or cause of action arises or it is barred. By using this site, you irrevocably submit to the jurisdiction of the State and Federal courts located nearest to Auburn, California. If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of these Terms to be unenforceable, that provision will be enforced to the maximum extent permissible so as to effect the intent of these Terms, and the remainder of these Terms will continue in full force and effect.
INTERNET FRAUD. In the interest of preventing Internet fraud, KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. reserves the right refuse to ship any order that is submitted with an untraceable or free email address, or an invalid telephone number.
PASSWORD AND USER NAME. Access to some content accessible from this Site is password controlled. By registering for an account, a password and the right to use this site, you are certifying that you are an authorized representative of your company with the right to bind your company to these Terms (and any additional terms necessary for access to password controlled content) and that all information provided in the registration process is accurate and correct. You further certify that any purchase orders placed by you are with the full authority to bind your company and any information provided by you in using any of the services accessible through this site is true and accurate. Your user name and password are unique to you or your company. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your user name, password and access to your account. You are solely responsible for all activities that occur under your user name and password. You agree to notify KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. immediately of any unauthorized use of your user name, password or account or any other breach of security. KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. will not be liable for any loss that you may incur as a result of someone else using your user name, password or account, either with or without your knowledge. But you may be held liable for losses incurred by KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. as a result of the misuse of your user name, password or account.
COMMENTS AND QUESTIONS. We appreciate your comments about our site. However, any comments, ideas, suggestions or other communications sent to the site become the sole property of KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc., and we may use all such communications in any manner, including reproducing, disclosing and publishing them, without compensation to you. If you have any questions or complaints, please contact us at contact@klsecurity.com
ENTIRE AGREEMENT. These Terms represent the entire agreement relating to the use of the Site. KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc.'s failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms does not constitute a waiver of that right or provision. KLSecurity.com, A Division of K.L. Security Enterprises, Inc. may revise these Terms at any time by updating this posting. Your continued use of this Site after the posting of any changes to these Terms constitutes your acceptance of those changes.
PROMOTIONS, OFFERS, REWARDS PROGRAM
We occasionally offer customers a variety of trial or other promotional offers, which are subject to these Terms except as otherwise stated in the promotional offers. We may at our discretion change these Terms, general Conditions of Use and Privacy Notice, or any aspect of the Rewards program, without notice to you. We may terminate your membership at our discretion without notice. If we do so, you will still be entitled to spend KLSecurity.com Rewards points earned under the program redemption terms. However, we will not allow redemption for termination related to conduct that we determine, in our discretion, violates these Terms or any applicable law, involves fraud or misuse of this program, or is harmful to our interests or another user. Our failure to insist upon or enforce your strict compliance with these Terms will not constitute a waiver of any of our rights. KLSecurity.com Rewards points will not be earned on gift certificate purchases.
To top
